<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
	===== GrimWorld 40,000 - Hammer of the Imperium =====
-->
<Patch>
    <Operation Class="XmlExtensions.FindMod">
        <mods>
            <li>grimworld.astramilitarum</li>
        </mods>
        <packageId>true</packageId>

        <caseTrue>
            <Operation Class="XmlExtensions.PatchOperationAdd">
                <xpath>Defs</xpath>
                <value>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" Name="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseMeleeWeapon_Sharp_Quality">
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                            <shaderType>CutoutComplex</shaderType>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
                        <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>IndustrialMeleeDecent</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <relicChance>2</relicChance>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainsword_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Militarum chainsword</label>
                        <description>The Militarum Chainsword, a quintessential close combat weapon within the Astra Militarum's vast armory, epitomizes the Imperium's relentless determination in the face of close-quarters engagements within the brutal and unforgiving battles of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nThis formidable melee weapon is a chainsaw-like implement, featuring a chain of monomolecular teeth powered by a high-torque motor. The Militarum Chainsword's primary function is to deliver swift, brutal, and efficient strikes in hand-to-hand combat. With its buzzing teeth capable of tearing through armor, flesh, and bone, the Chainsword is a symbol of the Astra Militarum's unwavering commitment to close combat effectiveness.\n\nWielded by the courageous soldiers of the Imperium, the Militarum Chainsword serves as a testament to the gritty determination of the Astra Militarum in the face of the galaxy's countless horrors. In the melee chaos of the 41st millennium, the Chainsword becomes an extension of the guardsman's will, embodying the unyielding spirit of the Imperial Guard as they stand against the darkness.\n\nWhether charging headlong into the enemy ranks or used as a last line of defense in desperate situations, the Militarum Chainsword remains a stalwart companion to the courageous soldiers of the Astra Militarum, ready to deliver the Emperor's justice in the form of whirring blades and unyielding resolve.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Chainsword</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>6</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>13.162</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.53</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>31.099</power>
                                <cooldownTime>2.04</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.44</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainshortsword_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Short chainsword</label>
                        <description>The Militarum Short Chainsword, a compact yet lethal incarnation of close combat prowess in the Astra Militarum's arsenal, symbolizes the Imperium's commitment to versatility and adaptability on the grim battlefields of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted for maneuverability and ease of use, the short chainsword features a truncated design without compromising its deadly efficiency. Its monomolecular teeth, driven by a high-torque motor, make it a formidable weapon in close-quarters engagements. The shortened length enhances the guardsman's agility, allowing for swift strikes and rapid responses in the heat of melee combat.\n\nIn the hands of the Astra Militarum, the Militarum Short Chainsword becomes a tool of relentless aggression, embodying the gritty determination and resourcefulness of the Imperial Guard. Whether clearing cramped corridors, engaging in urban warfare, or acting as a backup weapon in emergencies, this compact chainsword stands ready to deliver lethal blows against the enemies of the Imperium.\n\nAs the soldiers of the Astra Militarum navigate the treacherous landscapes of the 41st millennium, the Militarum Short Chainsword remains a symbol of adaptability, ensuring that the forces of the Imperium are always prepared for the unpredictable challenges that await them in the dark and war-torn galaxy.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Chain Shortsword</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>2.25</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>13.162</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.36</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>24.472</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.33</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseMeleeWeapon_Blunt_Quality" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_TrenchShovel_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Trench shovel</label>
                        <description>The Trench Shovel, revered as the favored close-quarters weapon of the Death Korps of Krieg, epitomizes the grim and relentless nature of the regiments hailing from the irradiated and war-torn planet.\n\nForged in the fires of Krieg's industrial complexes, the Trench Shovel serves as a multi-purpose tool for the Death Korps soldiers. Its sturdy construction allows it to withstand the harsh conditions of trench warfare and close combat. With a reinforced, sharpened blade on one side and a serrated edge on the other, the shovel transforms seamlessly from a digging implement to a formidable melee weapon.\n\nIn the hands of the Death Korps, the Trench Shovel becomes an extension of their unyielding will and unrelenting discipline. Whether it's breaching enemy fortifications, clearing obstacles, or engaging in brutal hand-to-hand combat, the Death Korps soldiers wield the Trench Shovel with ruthless efficiency.\n\nAs the regiments of Krieg march stoically into battle, the haunting echoes of the Trench Shovel striking against enemy armor and fortifications serve as a somber reminder of the brutal warfare endured by the Death Korps on their desolate home world. This utilitarian implement turned lethal weapon embodies the harsh pragmatism and indomitable spirit of the Death Korps of Krieg as they fulfill their duty to the God-Emperor in the grim darkness of the far future.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Trench Shovel</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
                        <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.5</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>IndustrialMeleeDecent</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>Melee</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>12.0</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>head</label>
                                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>21.907</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>22.243</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CombatKnife_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Combat knife</label>
                        <description>The Militarum Combat Knife, a staple among the Astra Militarum forces, stands as a testament to the practicality and versatility required by soldiers in the unforgiving battlegrounds of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nForged for durability and precision, the combat knife is a compact yet formidable blade. Its razor-sharp edge is ideal for a range of close-quarters engagements, making it an essential tool for Astra Militarum soldiers navigating the unpredictable landscapes of warfare. The serrated sections along the blade enhance its utility, allowing for effective use in various tactical situations.\n\nThe design of the Militarum Combat Knife incorporates a reinforced hilt and ergonomic grip, ensuring a secure hold even in the chaos of battle. Its compact size makes it a practical sidearm, allowing soldiers to carry it alongside their primary weaponry without hindrance.\n\nWhether used for stealthy incursions, survival situations, or as a last resort in hand-to-hand combat, the Militarum Combat Knife embodies the resilience and adaptability required by the soldiers of the Astra Militarum. In the grim darkness of the 41st millennium, where every inch of ground is contested, the combat knife is a symbol of the indomitable spirit and resourcefulness of the Imperial Guard.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/CombatKnife</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.0</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>13.162</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.36</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>17.742</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.53</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.275</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>point</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Stab</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>18.873</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.53</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.308</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CatachanFang_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Catachan fang</label>
                        <description>The Catachan Fang, revered among the mighty Catachan Jungle Fighters, is a deadly and iconic close combat weapon that reflects the raw power and primal skill of these renowned Imperial Guard soldiers.\n\nForged amidst the perilous jungles of Catachan, the Fang boasts a distinctive design. Its blade, crafted from exceptionally durable materials, features a serrated edge reminiscent of the dangers lurking within the dense foliage of Catachan's untamed wilderness. The Fang is not merely a weapon but a symbol of the Jungle Fighters' tenacity and ability to adapt to the formidable challenges they face.\n\nThe balance and heft of the Catachan Fang make it an ideal companion for the close-quarters engagements that Catachan warriors often find themselves entangled in. Its design allows for swift and precise strikes, capable of dealing devastating blows to adversaries in the blink of an eye.\n\nIn the hands of a Catachan Jungle Fighter, the Catachan Fang becomes an extension of the warrior's skill and determination. Whether slashing through dense vegetation or cutting down foes in the heat of battle, the Catachan Fang embodies the untamed spirit of Catachan's formidable soldiers as they defend the Imperium against the myriad threats of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/CatachanKnife</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.0</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>14.317</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.36</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>22.243</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.53</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.396</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>point</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Stab</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>20.0</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.53</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.418</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Eviscerator_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Eviscerator</label>
                        <description>The Eviscerator, a towering symbol of the Imperium's might, this monstrous chainsword cleaves through the enemies of humanity with relentless brutality, leaving a trail of devastation in the grim darkness of the 41st millennium's unending wars.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Eviscerator</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.0</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>25</equippedAngleOffset>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>24.472</power>
                                <cooldownTime>2.125</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>57.071</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.275</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>1.65</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>point</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Stab</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>13.162</power>
                                <cooldownTime>2.125</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.55</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" Name="MPBFPM_GW_AM_PowerSwordBase" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseMeleeWeapon_Sharp_Quality">
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <description>The Militarum Power Sword, a symbol of authority and lethal precision wielded by the disciplined forces of the Astra Militarum, embodies the fusion of martial prowess and advanced technology within the grim and war-torn universe of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nForged in the crucibles of Imperial manufactorums, the Power Sword is a masterfully crafted melee weapon. Its razor-sharp blade, sheathed in an energy field, crackles with a lethal charge capable of cutting through armor and flesh alike. This energy field not only enhances the sword's cutting power but also renders it a formidable weapon against even the most heavily armored adversaries.\n\nThe Power Sword serves as a potent symbol of command within the Astra Militarum, often carried by officers and leaders on the front lines. Its gleaming blade and hum of contained energy project an aura of authority and martial prowess, inspiring the soldiers of the Imperium to stand resolute in the face of the galaxy's myriad threats.\n\nIn the hands of a skilled Astra Militarum officer, the Power Sword becomes a versatile instrument of war, capable of delivering precise strikes and cleaving through the enemies of humanity. As the Imperium fights for survival, the Militarum Power Sword stands as a testament to the enduring might of the Astra Militarum in the grim darkness of the far future.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                            <shaderType>CutoutComplex</shaderType>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerMeleeDecent</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <relicChance>2</relicChance>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>17.742</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.36</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>point</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Stab</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>35.477</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>1.1</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>edge</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Cut</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>35.477</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>1.1</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseMeleeWeapon_Blunt_Quality" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerFist_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Militarum power fist</label>
                        <description>The Militarum Power Fist, a colossal and formidable melee weapon wielded by the mighty warriors of the Astra Militarum, is a symbol of raw, unbridled power and crushing force on the battlefield within the dark and unforgiving expanse of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nCrafted with uncompromising strength, the Power Fist is an oversized gauntlet encasing the user's hand and forearm. Embedded within its reinforced structure are powerful hydraulic systems and energy field generators. This combination grants the Power Fist unparalleled destructive capability, allowing it to deliver bone-crushing blows and obliterate heavily armored foes with ease.\n\nThough the Power Fist's size and weight slow the user's movements, its devastating impact compensates for the reduced agility. It is a close-quarters weapon, ideal for smashing through enemy lines and engaging formidable adversaries at point-blank range. The kinetic force generated by the Power Fist is often sufficient to crush armored vehicles, making it a favored choice against the armored war machines that threaten the Imperium.\n\nWielding the Power Fist requires both strength and skill, traits possessed by the most formidable warriors and commanders of the Astra Militarum. Its presence on the battlefield instills fear in the hearts of the enemies of the Imperium, as they face an unstoppable force that can shatter defenses and turn the tide of battle in favor of humanity. In the grim and perilous universe of Warhammer 40,000, the Militarum Power Fist stands as a testament to the unyielding might of the Astra Militarum.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Power Fist</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>4</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerMeleeDecent</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>Melee</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>Fist</label>
                                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>48.481</power>
                                <cooldownTime>2.55</cooldownTime>
                                <extraMeleeDamages>
                                    <li>
                                        <def>Bomb</def>
                                        <amount>3</amount>
                                    </li>
                                </extraMeleeDamages>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseMeleeWeapon_Blunt_Quality" Name="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerMaul_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Ogryn power maul</label>
                        <description>The Ogryn Power Maul, an imposing melee weapon wielded by the formidable Ogryn shock troops of the Astra Militarum, epitomizes raw power and devastating impact on the war-torn battlefields of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nCrafted to match the colossal strength of the Ogryns, the Power Maul is a massive, blunt instrument designed to deliver bone-crushing blows to adversaries. Enhanced with sturdy construction and powered by formidable hydraulic systems, the Power Maul is capable of generating tremendous force upon impact. It is particularly effective against heavily armored foes and in smashing through barricades and fortifications.\n\nThe sheer size and weight of the Power Maul contribute to the slow and deliberate movements of the Ogryn wielding it. While lacking the swiftness of smaller melee weapons, the Power Maul compensates with its ability to pulverize enemies in close-quarters combat. The weapon's impact can incapacitate foes, shatter armor, and disrupt enemy formations.\n\nUtilizing the Power Maul requires a combination of immense strength and calculated precision. The Ogryn shock troops, with their inherent physical might, are well-suited to leverage the full potential of this devastating melee weapon. On the battlefield, the presence of Ogryns armed with Power Mauls instills fear in the enemies of the Imperium, as they face a relentless force capable of smashing through any resistance.\n\nIn the grim and brutal universe of Warhammer 40,000, the Ogryn Power Maul stands as a symbol of the Astra Militarum's commitment to overwhelming force in the defense of humanity.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Power_Maul</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>4.8</Mass>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerMeleeDecent</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_PowerMaul</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPMelee</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerMelee</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>Melee</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>handle</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>20.0</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.488</cooldownTime>
                                <armorPenetration>0.264</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>head</label>
                                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>42.0</power>
                                <cooldownTime>2.763</cooldownTime>
                                <extraMeleeDamages>
                                    <li>
                                        <def>Bomb</def>
                                        <amount>5</amount>
                                    </li>
                                </extraMeleeDamages>
                                <armorPenetration>0.528</armorPenetration>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase">
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPAutoguns</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>HP_Autogun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_Agripinaamkii_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Agripinaa MKII</label>
                        <description>The Agripinaa MKII Autogun stands as a fearsome weapon within the Warhammer 40,000 universe, renowned for its devastating firepower and resilience. Crafted with meticulous detail, its design reflects a balance of robustness and efficiency to endure the harsh conditions of futuristic battlefields.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Agripinaa MKII</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Rifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.6</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.605</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.792</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.726</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.638</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.36</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.0</warmupTime>
                                <range>34</range>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Agripinaamkii</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Medium</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>AssaultRifle</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_Agripinaamkiitanker_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Tanker Agripinaa MKII</label>
                        <description>The Tanker Agripinaa MKII Autogun stands as a fearsome weapon within the Warhammer 40,000 universe, renowned for its devastating firepower and resilience. Crafted with meticulous detail, its design reflects a balance of robustness and efficiency to endure the harsh conditions of futuristic battlefields.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Tanker Agripinaa MKII</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Rifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.2</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.77</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.44</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.33</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.36</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.0</warmupTime>
                                <range>26</range>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Agripinaamkii</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Medium</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_OrlockAutogun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Orlock autogun</label>
                        <description>Amidst the grim battlegrounds of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Orlock Autogun emerges as a steadfast instrument of war in the hands of the Imperium's disciplined forces. Crafted with meticulous detail, this autogun features a utilitarian design and matte-black ceramite alloy exterior, embodying its reliability and efficiency on the front lines.\n\nThe Orlock Autogun operates as a rapid-firing and magazine-fed weapon, providing Astra Militarum infantry with a versatile tool for engaging a range of adversaries. Its pragmatic design and ease of use make it an essential firearm for the foot soldiers of the Imperium.\n\nWith each burst of sustained fire, the characteristic staccato of the autogun's report reverberates, a resounding declaration of the Imperium's firepower on the battlefield. In the hands of the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, the Orlock Autogun stands as a symbol of the Imperium's commitment to equipping its forces with reliable and effective weaponry, ensuring their resilience against the relentless threats in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Orlock Autogun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Rifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.6</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.88</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.66</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.33</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.187</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.445</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.4</warmupTime>
                                <range>24</range>
                                <burstShotCount>5</burstShotCount>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_OrlockAutogun</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Medium</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_Zarona_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Zarona MKII</label>
                        <description>In the unyielding theaters of Warhammer 40,000, the Astra Militarum Zarona MKII Stub Revolver ascends as a pinnacle of Imperial firepower, an epitome of technological supremacy. Meticulously crafted with precision engineering, this bolter features a sleek yet robust design, adorned with matte-black ceramite alloy, symbolizing its prowess on the battlefield.\n\nFunctioning as a rapid-firing, self-loading, and magazine-fed weapon, the Zarona MKII Bolter unleashes mass-reactive bolts with lethal precision. Its streamlined yet effective design makes it a preferred choice for Astra Militarum forces seeking a versatile and dependable firearm for various combat scenarios.\n\nAugmenting its versatility, the Zarona MKII incorporates a stub revolver mechanism, providing a secondary mode of engagement for Astra Militarum troops. This dual functionality enhances the bolter's adaptability in close-quarters engagements, where swift and decisive action is paramount.\n\nWith each calculated shot, the distinctive report of mass-reactive bolts and the resolute rotation of the stub revolver echo, underscoring the Zarona MKII Bolter's role as a formidable force on the front lines. In the hands of the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, this bolter stands as a symbol of the Imperium's unwavering commitment to excellence in armament, ensuring the Imperium's dominance against the myriad threats in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Zarona MKII</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.4</uiIconScale>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Revolver</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.77</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.715</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.473</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.275</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.53</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>Revolver</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedLight</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Stubround_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1</warmupTime>
                                <range>25.9</range>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Zarona</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Light</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_Hiveworldautopistol_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Hiveworld autopistol</label>
                        <description>In the tumultuous battlegrounds of Warhammer 40,000, the Astra Militarum Hiveworld Autopistol emerges as a testament to the Imperium's adaptability in the face of relentless threats. Crafted with meticulous detail, this autopistol features a utilitarian design and matte-black ceramite alloy exterior, embodying its resilience and efficiency in the harsh environments of hive worlds.\n\nFunctioning as a semi-automatic sidearm, the Hiveworld Autopistol serves as a reliable companion for Astra Militarum forces navigating the crowded and perilous corridors of hive cities. Its compact design and ease of use make it a preferred choice for close-quarter engagements, where rapid response is imperative.\n\nThe distinctive report of each controlled shot resonates through the narrow confines of hive cities, marking the Hiveworld Autopistol as a symbol of the Imperium's commitment to equipping its forces with versatile and effective sidearms. In the hands of Astra Militarum troops, this autopistol stands as a testament to the Imperium's resourcefulness and determination to prevail in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>0.8</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Hiveworld Autopistol</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.4</uiIconScale>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Autopistol</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedLight</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>2.5</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.88</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.77</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.44</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.33</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Autopistolgrim_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1</warmupTime>
                                <range>18</range>
                                <burstShotCount>5</burstShotCount>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>7</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Hiveworldautopistol</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Light</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_Heavystubber_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Heavy stubber</label>
                        <description>Amidst the chaos and carnage of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Heavy Stubber stands resolute as a bastion of suppressive firepower. Imbued with the Imperium's relentless determination to assert dominance on the battlefield, this heavy weapon is a manifestation of sheer lethality.\n\nCrafted with uncompromising precision, the Heavy Stubber boasts a robust design, featuring a matte-black ceramite alloy frame that signifies both its durability and unyielding power. Functioning as a belt-fed machine gun, the Heavy Stubber is a stalwart companion for Astra Militarum forces engaged in protracted firefights.\n\nThe weapon's distinctive report echoes across the battlefield, drowning out the clamor of war with each controlled burst. Deployed to provide sustained covering fire, the Heavy Stubber is a symbol of the Imperium's commitment to overwhelming firepower and strategic superiority.\n\nIn the hands of Astra Militarum gunners, this heavy weapon becomes a force multiplier, turning the tide of battle with its ability to suppress enemy advances and fortify Imperial positions. The Astra Militarum Heavy Stubber is an indomitable presence, ensuring that the Imperium's adversaries cower in the face of its unrelenting might in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Heavy Stubber</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Rifle</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>12</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.374</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.528</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.462</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.286</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.275</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.50</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Stubround_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>2</warmupTime>
                                <range>27.9</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>9</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>9</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Hiveworldautopistol</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Medium</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_MilitarumShotgun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Militarum shotgun</label>
                        <description>In the grim and perilous expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Shotgun emerges as a versatile and close-quarters weapon, perfectly suited for the harrowing engagements that define the Imperium's perpetual struggle. Imbued with the essence of pragmatism, this scattergun combines simplicity with brutal efficiency.\n\nThe Astra Militarum Shotgun's design features a rugged construction, utilizing durable materials to withstand the unforgiving conditions of the battlefield. Its matte-black ceramite finish not only adds to its utilitarian aesthetic but also symbolizes the unyielding resolve of the Imperium in the face of relentless adversity.\n\nAs a pump-action firearm, the Shotgun excels in short-range encounters, providing Astra Militarum troops with a formidable tool for breaching enemy defenses and navigating the treacherous environments of war-torn worlds. The distinctive sound of each shell being chambered serves as a prelude to the devastation that follows.\n\nDeployed by the Astra Militarum forces, the Shotgun becomes a testament to adaptability, offering both lethal stopping power and practicality in the unpredictable theatre of war. Whether clearing tight corridors or engaging in brutal urban combat, the Astra Militarum Shotgun stands as a steadfast companion, ensuring the Imperium's dominance in the grim and relentless galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>0.8</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Militarum Shotgun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Shotgun</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.88</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.924</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.55</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.062</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.9</warmupTime>
                                <range>18</range>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_MilitarumShotgun</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="Gun_MilitarumShotgunSawn_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Sawn-off militarum shotgun</label>
                        <description>In the brutal theatres of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sawn-Off Militarum Shotgun emerges as a visceral and ruthless close-quarters weapon, embodying the grim determination of Astra Militarum forces engaged in the perpetual struggle against the galaxy's myriad threats. Stripped down to its brutal essentials, this sawn-off variant is a testament to the brutal pragmatism required in the crucible of war.\n\nThe Sawn-Off Militarum Shotgun retains the rugged and durable construction of its standard counterpart, but its shortened barrel and compact design make it a lethal tool for engagements where proximity is the defining factor. The matte-black ceramite finish, symbolic of the Imperium's unyielding might, adorns this brutal firearm.\n\nAs a double-barreled, close-quarters weapon, the Sawn-Off Shotgun unleashes devastating power with each thunderous blast. Its abbreviated form is an embodiment of the Imperium's uncompromising stance in the face of adversity, as Astra Militarum forces wield it to turn the tide in their favor in the relentless struggle against the forces that threaten humanity.\n\nDeployed in the chaotic and claustrophobic environments of urban warfare or subterranean battles, the Sawn-Off Militarum Shotgun becomes a symbol of raw, unbridled force&#8212;a grim harbinger for those who stand against the Imperium in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>0.8</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Sawn Off Militarum Shotgun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Shotgun</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.99</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.88</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.462</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.33</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.275</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.6</warmupTime>
                                <range>12</range>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_MilitarumShotgunSawn</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_AutogunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Rippergun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Ripper Gun</label>
                        <description>In the grim and expansive battlefield of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Ripper Gun wielded by Ogryns stands as a brutish and formidable testament to the raw power harnessed by the forces of the Imperium. Embodying the sheer might of these hulking warriors, the Ripper Gun becomes a fearsome tool in the ceaseless struggle against the galaxy's relentless adversaries.\n\nThe Ripper Gun is an immense and robust projectile weapon, tailored to the immense strength and size of the Ogryns. Its construction melds function with brawn, featuring a sturdy frame and reinforced components that ensure the weapon can withstand the punishing demands of close-quarters engagements. The unmistakable metallic sheen of the weapon serves as a visual declaration of the Ogryns' unyielding allegiance to the Imperium.\n\nAs a fully automatic projectile weapon, the Ripper Gun unleashes a torrent of firepower with each squeeze of the trigger. Its primary ammunition, capable of tearing through both infantry and lightly armored adversaries, is a relentless force on the battlefield. The distinctive roar of the Ripper Gun serves as a grim harbinger, signaling the impending onslaught as Ogryns charge headlong into the heart of the enemy.\n\nWielded by the Ogryns, these mighty warriors clad in heavy armor, the Ripper Gun becomes an extension of their indomitable strength&#8212;a symbol of the Imperium's willingness to unleash formidable firepower to secure its dominance in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Rippergun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Shotgun</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                            <li>GW_Rippergun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>8.4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>1.045</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.44</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.22</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.275</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.9</warmupTime>
                                <range>16</range>
                                <burstShotCount>4</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_MilitarumShotgun</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseGunWithQuality" Name="MPBFPM_HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase">
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <relicChance>3</relicChance>
                        <statBases>
                            <MarketValue>1320.0</MarketValue>
                        </statBases>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>ExoticMisc</li>
                            <li>Artifact</li>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelsanctified_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Sanctified Kantrael MG</label>
                        <description>In the shadowy corners of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified Kantrael MG emerges as an artifact of unparalleled potency, its name echoing through the annals of the Imperium's grim history. Infused with sacred purpose and bathed in the sanctity of the Emperor's light, this mighty relic stands as a beacon of divine retribution against the myriad threats that beset the Imperium.\n\nThe Sanctified Kantrael MG, a manifestation of the Omnissiah's grace, is a relic of forgotten origin. Its intricately adorned chassis is adorned with sacred inscriptions and symbols, testifying to its consecrated nature. The weapon's components are said to have been blessed by the Tech-Priests of Mars, imbuing it with both mechanical precision and divine fervor.\n\nAs a manifestation of the Machine God's will, the Sanctified Kantrael MG unleashes a hail of righteous fury upon the enemies of the Imperium. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by arcane mechanisms, cut through heretics and xenos alike with unerring accuracy. The unmistakable hum of the weapon's consecrated components adds an otherworldly aura to the cacophony of battle.\n\nIn the hands of a faithful servant of the Imperium, the Sanctified Kantrael MG becomes a divine instrument of purgation, smiting the foes of mankind with relentless zeal. Its sanctified nature marks it as more than a mere weapon&#8212;it is a relic, a conduit of the Emperor's wrath, wielded in the eternal struggle against the encroaching darkness of the Warhammer 40,000 galaxy.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified Kantrael MG</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.715</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.88</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.99</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.935</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.275</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <Beauty>5</Beauty>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.90</warmupTime>
                                <range>40.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefoursanctified_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Sanctified MK4 lascarbine</label>
                        <description>In the grim and unyielding expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine emerges as a sacred artifact, a symbol of unwavering devotion and the Emperor's divine protection. Crafted with meticulous care and blessed by the Ecclesiarchy, this relic stands as a beacon of faith and righteous fury against the myriad enemies that threaten the Imperium.\n\nThe Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine's origins are shrouded in the mysteries of the Ecclesiarchy's sanctuaries. Its sleek and ornate design, adorned with sacred inscriptions and symbols of purity, signifies its consecrated nature. Each component is said to have been anointed in holy oils and subjected to rituals of benediction, infusing the weapon with the very essence of the Emperor's divine grace.\n\nAs a manifestation of the Emperor's will, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine delivers death to heretics and xenos alike. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by the sanctified mechanisms within, strike with unerring accuracy, leaving a trail of purifying flame in their wake. The weapon's unmistakable discharge echoes the liturgy of the faithful, a symphony of devotion in the heat of battle.\n\nIn the hands of a devoted servant of the Imperium, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine becomes a conduit of righteous wrath, purging the enemies of mankind with unrelenting zeal. Its sanctified nature transforms it into more than a mere firearm&#8212;it is a relic, a sacred instrument wielded in the eternal struggle to safeguard humanity from the malevolent forces that lurk in the darkness of the Warhammer 40,000 galaxy.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.66</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.935</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.715</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.977</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <Beauty>5</Beauty>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.80</warmupTime>
                                <range>30.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>2</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_VossPatternsanctified_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Sanctified Voss MKI</label>
                        <description>In the somber and desolate tapestry of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified Voss MKI stands as a revered artifact, a testament to the indomitable spirit of the Imperium and the unyielding resolve of its defenders. This sacred relic, steeped in the traditions of the Adeptus Mechanicus, embodies the fusion of technology and divine veneration.\n\nForged in the sanctified foundries of Mars, the Sanctified Voss MKI is an intricate masterpiece, its mechanical intricacies meticulously crafted and adorned with arcane symbols of the Machine God's favor. Each component, from its blessed barrel to the sacred firing mechanism, has undergone sacred rites and consecration, elevating it beyond the realm of mundane weaponry.\n\nThe Sanctified Voss MKI operates on the sacred principles of the Omnissiah, delivering bolts of righteous fury with unerring precision. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by the holy machinations within, pierce through the darkness with a luminous trail, leaving naught but purifying flame in their wake. The weapon's discharge resonates like a liturgical hymn, a harmonious symphony of reverence and destruction.\n\nWielded by the faithful Tech-Priests of the Adeptus Mechanicus, the Sanctified Voss MKI becomes a conduit of the Machine God's divine will. Its presence on the battlefield is a manifestation of the Omnissiah's blessings, striking down the enemies of the Imperium with calculated and relentless force. As an artifact, the Sanctified Voss MKI is more than a tool of war&#8212;it is a sacred relic, a testament to the enduring alliance between man and machine in the eternal struggle against the darkness that engulfs the galaxy.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified Voss MKI</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.2</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.605</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.935</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.715</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <Beauty>5</Beauty>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.20</warmupTime>
                                <range>34.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>5</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" Name="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun">
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>GW_AM_Lasgun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_Lasguns</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Kantrael MG</label>
                        <description>The Kantrael MG, sanctified and embraced by the indomitable Cadian Shock Troops, becomes an even more imposing force on the battlefield. In the hands of the steadfast Cadian warriors, this malevolent weapon is wielded with unwavering discipline and precision, a testament to the renowned marksmanship and unyielding resolve of the Cadian Shock Troops.\n\nAdorned with the iconic regalia of the Cadian regiments, the Kantrael MG bears the distinctive markings of Cadian pride. The stark lines of the lasgun meld seamlessly with the rugged aesthetic of the Cadian war machine, creating a fusion of efficiency and military grandeur. Each pull of the trigger resonates with the disciplined cadence instilled in every Cadian soldier from the moment they step foot onto the battlefield.\n\nAs the Kantrael MG spits forth its malefic projectiles, the Cadian Shock Troops move in unison, executing precise tactical maneuvers that have been drilled into them through countless training exercises. The seamless coordination between the weapon and its wielders transforms the battlefield into a symphony of destruction, with the Cadian forces orchestrating a deadly ballet of firepower.\n\nEmblematic of the Cadian Shock Troops' unwavering dedication to the Imperium, the Kantrael MG becomes a symbol of the regiment's unbreakable spirit. With the weapon in their hands, the Cadian soldiers stand resolute against the myriad threats that seek to unravel the fabric of the Imperium. The Kantrael MG, sanctified in the fires of conflict, serves as a beacon of hope and an instrument of retribution, ensuring that the enemies of the Imperium are met with the unyielding might of the Cadian Shock Troops.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Kantrael MG</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.66</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.935</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.825</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.445</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.00</warmupTime>
                                <range>35.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelt_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Kantrael MG-t</label>
                        <description>The Kantrael MG-T, the Tertium variant of this revered weapon, stands as a testament to the adaptability and ingenuity of the Astra Militarum, particularly the esteemed Cadian Shock Troops. In the crucible of warfare, where versatility is paramount, the Kantrael MG-T emerges as a formidable tool tailored to the specific needs of the Cadian forces.\n\nInfused with the technological advancements of the Adeptus Mechanicus, the Kantrael MG-T incorporates cutting-edge modifications that elevate its functionality on the battlefield. The tertiary variant introduces enhanced targeting systems, allowing for improved accuracy and target acquisition. The addition of specialized ammunition feeds ensures seamless transitions between different projectile types, providing the Cadian Shock Troops with unparalleled adaptability in the face of diverse threats.\n\nThe rugged yet refined design of the Kantrael MG-T mirrors the disciplined nature of the Cadian Shock Troops. Adorned with the heraldic symbols of the Cadian regiments, this variant maintains the iconic aesthetic that signifies the indomitable spirit of the Cadian forces. The integration of auxiliary components, such as telescopic stocks and ergonomic grips, enhances the weapon's maneuverability and ensures optimal performance in a variety of combat scenarios.\n\nAs the Cadian Shock Troops deploy the Kantrael MG-T on the front lines, the weapon becomes a linchpin in their tactical arsenal. Whether suppressing enemy advances or delivering precision fire support, the Tertium variant stands as a beacon of the Astra Militarum's adaptability and resilience. In the hands of the Cadian Shock Troops, the Kantrael MG-T exemplifies the synthesis of tradition and innovation, embodying the unwavering commitment to defend the Imperium against the encroaching darkness.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Kantrael MG-t</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.715</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.55</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.19</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedLight</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWELMG_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.00</warmupTime>
                                <range>28.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona MK4 lascarbine</label>
                        <description>The Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine, a sacred relic wielded by the renowned Catachan Jungle Fighters, epitomizes the fusion of rugged durability and deadly precision tailored for the perilous environments of dense jungles and hostile terrains.\n\nForged in the crucible of Catachan's unforgiving wilderness, the MK4 Lascarbine serves as an extension of the indomitable spirit of the Catachan Jungle Fighters. Its compact and lightweight design allows for exceptional maneuverability through thick vegetation, while the specialized materials and coatings protect the weapon from the corrosive effects of the jungle's humidity and flora.\n\nAdorned with the distinctive markings of Catachan regiments, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine is a symbol of pride and resilience. The Catachan Jungle Fighters, known for their exceptional marksmanship, rely on the weapon's precise targeting systems to navigate the intricate and perilous jungle terrain. The Sanctified variant incorporates sacred blessings, ensuring the weapon's functionality remains unwavering even in the heart of the Catachan wilderness.\n\nFeaturing a collapsible stock for ease of transport and rapid deployment, the MK4 Lascarbine enables the Catachan Jungle Fighters to maintain the element of surprise in their guerrilla tactics. The weapon's semi-automatic firing mode provides controlled bursts, conserving ammunition while delivering lethal accuracy against adversaries hidden amidst the dense foliage.\n\nAs the Catachan Jungle Fighters traverse the hostile jungles, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine becomes an extension of their skill and tenacity. In the hands of these elite warriors, the weapon embodies the spirit of Catachan, standing as a testament to their adaptability and unyielding commitment to defending the Imperium from the myriad threats that lurk within the untamed wilderness.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/MK4 Lascarbine</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.605</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.88</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.715</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.66</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.147</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.2</warmupTime>
                                <range>26.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>2</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Voss MKI</label>
                        <description>The Voss MKI, a staple weapon in the arsenal of the Armageddon Steel Legion, stands as a testament to the regiment's adaptability and resilience in the face of the harsh conditions and relentless warfare on the desolate industrial hellscape of Armageddon.\n\nCrafted to withstand the corrosive effects of constant ash storms and industrial pollutants, the Voss MKI is a rugged and durable lasgun that has become synonymous with the Armageddon Steel Legion's signature style of warfare. The weapon's matte black finish and reinforced components not only enhance its durability but also contribute to the Legion's iconic aesthetic.\n\nThe Voss MKI features a semi-automatic firing mode, allowing for precise targeting and controlled bursts that are crucial in the urban warfare scenarios prevalent on Armageddon. Its adaptable design incorporates a folding stock, enabling ease of use in tight spaces and facilitating swift transitions between close-quarters combat and ranged engagements.\n\nThe lasgun's energy-efficient power cell is optimized for prolonged missions in Armageddon's war-torn environments, ensuring the Armageddon Steel Legionnaires can maintain sustained firefights against the relentless hordes of enemies that assail their homeworld.\n\nEmblazoned with the heraldic symbols of the Armageddon Steel Legion, the Voss MKI serves not just as a tool of war but as a symbol of the Legion's unyielding dedication to defending their homeworld from the ceaseless threats that emerge from the twisted landscapes of Armageddon. In the hands of the Steel Legionnaires, the Voss MKI embodies the regiment's indomitable spirit and steadfast commitment to the Imperium's cause.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Voss MKI</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.2</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.55</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.715</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.605</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.19</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.40</warmupTime>
                                <range>30.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Accatranfive_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Accatran MKIV</label>
                        <description>The Accatran MKIV, revered as the primary weapon of the Elysian Drop Troops, exemplifies the airborne regiment's commitment to swift and precise military operations in the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted with meticulous attention to detail and functionality, the Accatran MKIV is specifically designed for the unique challenges of aerial insertion and rapid deployment. As the Elysian Drop Troops often engage in high-altitude drops behind enemy lines, the lasgun's lightweight construction ensures minimal encumbrance during descent, allowing the troopers to maintain agility and maneuverability upon landing.\n\nThe weapon features a compact yet powerful design, incorporating a bullpup configuration to maximize barrel length while minimizing overall size. This layout enhances accuracy and muzzle velocity, crucial factors in the Elysian Drop Troops' fast-paced and dynamic combat scenarios.\n\nThe Accatran MKIV's selective fire modes&#8212;semi-automatic for precision shots and fully automatic for suppressive fire&#8212;provide the Elysian troopers with versatility on the battlefield. This adaptability is essential for engaging various threats encountered during airborne operations.\n\nThe lasgun's integral scope and targeting system are calibrated for pinpoint accuracy, aiding the Elysian Drop Troops in swiftly neutralizing priority targets upon landing. Additionally, the weapon's streamlined silhouette facilitates ease of use in confined spaces, making it an ideal choice for close-quarters combat during urban engagements.\n\nAdorned with the distinctive iconography of the Elysian Drop Troops, the Accatran MKIV is more than a weapon; it symbolizes the regiment's commitment to executing lightning-fast aerial assaults and exemplifies their role as elite shock troopers within the vast and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Accatran MKIV</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.2</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.935</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.704</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.385</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.22</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.36</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_LasboltACC_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.40</warmupTime>
                                <range>23.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>6</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>6</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Accatranfive</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Lucius_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Lucius MKI</label>
                        <description>The Lucius MKI, a revered weapon among the Death Korps of Krieg, stands as a testament to the regiment's unwavering commitment to relentless warfare in the grim darkness of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nForged in the fires of Krieg's industrial might, the Lucius MKI represents the epitome of rugged and reliable lasgun technology. Deployed across the desolate and war-torn landscapes of Krieg, this lasgun is meticulously crafted to endure the harsh conditions and protracted battles that define the Death Korps' relentless campaigns.\n\nThe Lucius MKI features a robust design, characterized by its durable construction and utilitarian aesthetics. The lasgun's heavy-duty frame is tailored to withstand the unforgiving environments of Krieg, ensuring that it remains operational even in the most inhospitable conditions.\n\nEquipped with a powerful and efficient energy cell, the Lucius MKI delivers consistent and potent las blasts, providing Death Korps infantry with the firepower needed to engage adversaries across the war-ravaged battlefields they tread. The lasgun's modular design allows for ease of maintenance and repairs in the field, a crucial aspect for the Death Korps as they endure protracted campaigns far from supply lines.\n\nThe Lucius MKI's design emphasizes functionality and reliability over ornate embellishments, aligning with the Death Korps' austere and disciplined approach to warfare. Its streamlined form and straightforward controls enable troopers to swiftly and efficiently engage targets, embodying the regiment's commitment to efficiency in the face of unrelenting conflict.\n\nAdorned with the iconic insignia of the Death Korps of Krieg, the Lucius MKI is not merely a weapon but a symbol of the regiment's unyielding resolve and willingness to sacrifice for the glory of the Imperium in the tumultuous galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Lucius MKI</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.715</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.88</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.99</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.88</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>2.04</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolttwo_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>2.5</warmupTime>
                                <range>37.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Lucius</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefender_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Kantrael MG Defender</label>
                        <description>The Kantrael MG Defender, an esteemed weapon wielded by the officers of the Cadian Shock Troopers, exemplifies the disciplined and battle-hardened nature of the Cadian regiments within the expansive Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted to meet the exacting standards of Cadian military excellence, the Kantrael MG Defender serves as a symbol of the regiment's commitment to unyielding defense and unwavering loyalty to the Imperium. Its robust design reflects the harsh conditions of the Cadian sector, where unrelenting warfare is a constant reality.\n\nThe Kantrael MG Defender boasts a formidable presence on the battlefield, featuring a heavy-duty construction that ensures reliability in the face of relentless combat. Engineered for defensive maneuvers, this heavy machine gun delivers a sustained hail of suppressive fire, allowing Cadian Shock Troopers to hold strategic positions and repel enemy advances with steadfast determination.\n\nEquipped with a precision targeting system, the Kantrael MG Defender enables Cadian officers to direct their troops with lethal efficiency. The weapon's advanced optics and enhanced stability contribute to its accuracy, making it a valuable asset in the hands of Cadian Shock Trooper leaders during intense firefights.\n\nThe iconic Cadian color scheme and regimental insignia adorn the Kantrael MG Defender, underscoring its affiliation with the disciplined ranks of the Cadian Shock Troopers. As a weapon of authority and command, the Kantrael MG Defender reinforces the leadership's role in orchestrating the strategic brilliance for which the Cadian regiments are renowned.\n\nIn the tumultuous galaxy of Warhammer 40,000, the Kantrael MG Defender stands as a testament to the Cadian Shock Troopers' indomitable spirit and their commitment to standing firm against the myriad threats that imperil the Imperium.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Kantrael MG Defender</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.5</uiIconScale>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Autopistol</soundInteract>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>Autopistol</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedLight</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.6</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.858</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.836</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.44</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.33</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmall_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.3</warmupTime>
                                <range>24.0</range>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefender</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefendert_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Kantrael MG-t Defender</label>
                        <description>The Kantrael MG-t Defender, a distinctive sidearm employed on the war-torn world of Tertium, epitomizes the adaptability and resilience of the forces fighting in the harsh environments within the expansive Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nDesigned to complement the diverse combat scenarios encountered on Tertium, the Kantrael MG-t Defender serves as a formidable secondary weapon for individuals operating in the unpredictable and challenging landscapes of the planet. Its compact size and versatile functionality make it well-suited for the close-quarters engagements and rapid response required in Tertium's dynamic theaters of war.\n\nThe Kantrael MG-t Defender boasts a sleek and streamlined design, allowing for ease of carry and maneuverability in Tertium's varied terrains. Despite its smaller frame, this pistol maintains the robust construction and firepower characteristic of its larger counterparts, providing a reliable means of self-defense for those navigating the perils of Tertium's battlegrounds.\n\nFeaturing specialized modifications for Tertium's distinct challenges, the Kantrael MG-t Defender excels in delivering controlled bursts of firepower. Its quick-draw capabilities and rapid target acquisition make it a preferred sidearm for individuals navigating the intricate urban landscapes or confronting adversaries in the dense and hazardous environments that define Tertium's combat zones.\n\nThe pistol bears markings and embellishments reflective of Tertium's unique culture and the gritty resilience of its fighters. Whether wielded by local defenders or interstellar warriors adapting to the planet's demands, the Kantrael MG-t Defender embodies the fusion of cutting-edge technology and practical design required to navigate the perilous battlegrounds of Tertium.\n\nIn the tumultuous expanse of Warhammer 40,000, the Kantrael MG-t Defender stands as a symbol of adaptability, offering a potent sidearm solution tailored to the challenges presented by Tertium's war-ravaged landscapes.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Kantrael MG-t Defender</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <uiIconScale>1.5</uiIconScale>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Autopistol</soundInteract>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>Autopistol</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedLight</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>1.6</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.858</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.836</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.44</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.33</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.68</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmalll_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.3</warmupTime>
                                <range>24.0</range>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefender</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Hellgun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Ryza Hellgun</label>
                        <description>The Ryza Hellgun, a potent and iconic firearm, is emblematic of the advanced technology and formidable firepower harnessed by the Astra Militarum forces associated with the Forge World of Ryza in the expansive Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted with precision and superior engineering, the Ryza Hellgun stands as a testament to the technological prowess of Ryza's adeptus mechanicus. This rapid-firing, energy-based weapon is designed to deliver devastating bursts of focused energy projectiles, making it a preferred choice for Astra Militarum troopers facing a diverse array of adversaries.\n\nThe Ryza Hellgun's distinctive design incorporates advanced plasma technology, channeling the raw power of plasma energy into lethal bolts that can penetrate a variety of armored targets. This makes it a versatile and effective tool on the battlefield, capable of engaging both infantry and heavily armored foes with equal ferocity.\n\nAdorned with the heraldry and symbols of Ryza, the Hellgun serves not only as a powerful tool of war but also as a symbol of the forge world's contribution to the Imperium's military might. The weapon's sleek lines, reinforced construction, and expert craftsmanship reflect the meticulous care taken by Ryza's tech-priests in ensuring the reliability and efficiency of each Hellgun produced.\n\nWielded by the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, the Ryza Hellgun embodies the fusion of cutting-edge technology and martial strength, making it a formidable asset in the ceaseless conflicts of the grim darkness of the 41st millennium. Whether deployed in the defense of the Imperium or as part of an advancing infantry line, the Ryza Hellgun stands ready to unleash the fiery wrath of Ryza upon the enemies of humanity.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Hellgun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>7.4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.44</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.528</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.385</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.286</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.7</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Hellbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>1.20</warmupTime>
                                <range>30.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>8</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>12</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Hellgun</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Locke_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Locke MKI</label>
                        <description>The Locke MKI Lightweight Lascarbine, a sleek and nimble firearm, represents a compact yet deadly addition to the armory of Astra Militarum forces in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nEngineered for agility and versatility, the Locke MKI is designed to provide Astra Militarum troopers with a lightweight yet potent ranged option. Its compact frame and reduced weight make it an ideal choice for mobile warfare, allowing soldiers to maintain speed and agility without sacrificing firepower.\n\nThe Locke MKI Lascarbine features a streamlined design, incorporating advanced materials and ergonomic considerations. The weapon's shortened barrel and overall compact profile make it easy to wield in tight quarters and well-suited for urban combat scenarios.\n\nDespite its reduced size, the Locke MKI doesn't compromise on stopping power. Utilizing energy-based projectiles, this carbine delivers precise and rapid bursts of firepower, making it effective against a variety of targets, from enemy infantry to lightly armored foes.\n\nEmblazoned with the markings and heraldry of the Astra Militarum, the Locke MKI reflects the adaptability and resourcefulness required in the unforgiving battles of the 41st millennium. Whether carried by scouting units, reconnaissance teams, or specialized infantry forces, the Locke MKI Lightweight Lascarbine stands as a testament to the Imperium's commitment to arming its soldiers with cutting-edge technology.\n\nIn the hands of the brave men and women of the Astra Militarum, the Locke MKI serves as a symbol of resilience and adaptability, embodying the Imperium's determination to face the myriad threats that assail it from every corner of the galaxy.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Locke MKI</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.3</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.693</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.88</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.99</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.88</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.105</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWELMG_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.80</warmupTime>
                                <range>35.0</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>6</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Locke</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_LasgunBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Longlas_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Longlas</label>
                        <description>The Longlas, a lasgun variant transformed into a precision sniper rifle, stands as a testament to the Astra Militarum's commitment to adapting their weaponry for long-range precision engagements in the grim and perilous battles of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted with meticulous attention to detail, the Longlas combines the reliability of the standard lasgun with specialized modifications tailored for sniper roles. The weapon features an extended barrel for enhanced accuracy, a high-powered optic system for superior target acquisition, and additional stabilization mechanisms to reduce recoil during precise shots.\n\nThe Longlas excels in providing accurate and lethal firepower at extended ranges, making it an ideal choice for marksmen and sharpshooters within the Astra Militarum ranks. Its energy-based projectiles offer consistent performance without the need for conventional ammunition, ensuring troopers can maintain a sustained rate of fire without the logistical challenges associated with traditional sniper rifles.\n\nAdorned with the symbols and regalia of the Astra Militarum, the Longlas embodies the discipline and skill required for precision marksmanship in the service of the Imperium. Deployed in the hands of specially trained snipers, this lasgun variant plays a crucial role in eliminating high-value targets, disrupting enemy formations, and providing cover fire for advancing Astra Militarum forces.\n\nIn the unrelenting warfare of Warhammer 40,000, the Longlas stands as a symbol of the Imperium's adaptability, using technology and innovation to overcome the myriad threats that plague the galaxy. Whether deployed in urban environments, open battlefields, or hostile alien landscapes, the Longlas serves as a deadly tool in the arsenal of the Astra Militarum, striking fear into the hearts of those who dare oppose the might of the Imperium of Man.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/LongLas</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>4</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.473</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.682</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.946</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>1.012</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.7</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>LongShots</li>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_LongLas</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolttwo_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>3.2</warmupTime>
                                <range>46</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Longlas</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="HP_AM_Gun_PlasmaGun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Astra Militarum plasma gun</label>
                        <description>Within the vast expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Plasma Gun stands as a pinnacle of advanced technology and devastating firepower, wielded by the disciplined forces of the Imperium. Crafted with meticulous engineering, this formidable weapon features a matte-black ceramite alloy construction, symbolizing its resilience amidst the ceaseless chaos of the galactic battleground.\n\nOperating as a rapid-firing and energy-based firearm, the Plasma Gun projects searing blasts of superheated plasma, capable of melting through armor and incinerating adversaries. Its versatile nature allows it to be effective at both short and mid-range engagements, making it an indispensable asset in the tactical arsenal of the Astra Militarum.\n\nThe distinctive hum of ionized energy accompanies each discharge, a herald of the Plasma Gun's destructive potential. Wielded by the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, this weapon symbolizes the Imperium's commitment to technological superiority and unyielding firepower in the perpetual war against heresy and alien threats in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/PlasmaGun</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>5.5</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.99</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.935</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.825</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.77</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerRanged</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>HP_AM_Bullet_PlasmaShot_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>3</warmupTime>
                                <range>40</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <forcedMissRadius>1.9</forcedMissRadius>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>HP_AM_Plasma_Gun_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                                <targetParams>
                                    <canTargetLocations>true</canTargetLocations>
                                </targetParams>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="HP_AM_Gun_MeltaGun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Astra Militarum meltagun</label>
                        <description>Amidst the tumultuous expanses of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Melta Gun emerges as a beacon of concentrated heat and destructive power wielded by the indomitable forces of the Imperium. Forged with precision and purpose, this formidable weapon features a matte-black ceramite alloy construction, a testament to its durability and reliability in the brutal theater of war.\n\nFunctioning as a close-range and anti-armor firearm, the Melta Gun projects concentrated beams of intense thermal energy, capable of liquefying armor and immolating even the most heavily fortified targets. Its design embodies versatility, allowing for devastating assaults on enemy vehicles and structures, making it a critical asset in the strategic repertoire of the Astra Militarum.\n\nEach discharge resonates with a distinctive hiss, heralding the Melta Gun's ability to turn the tide of battle with its unparalleled thermal devastation. In the hands of the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, this weapon stands as a testament to the Imperium's commitment to overwhelming firepower and technological supremacy in the ceaseless struggle against heresy and alien adversaries in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/MeltaGun</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>5</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.99</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.77</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.55</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.7</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.20</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerRanged</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>HP_AM_Bullet_MeltaGun_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>3</warmupTime>
                                <range>16</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <forcedMissRadius>1</forcedMissRadius>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>HP_AM_Melta_Gun_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>stock</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>9.75</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Ryza plasma pistol</label>
                        <description>In the unforgiving expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Astra Militarum Ryza Plasma Pistol emerges as a beacon of precision and power, brandished by the valiant soldiers of the Imperium. Forged with meticulous craftsmanship, this sidearm boasts a matte-black ceramite alloy exterior, signifying its resilience in the relentless crucible of combat.\n\nOperating as a sidearm of choice for those who demand both versatility and lethality, the Ryza Plasma Pistol propels searing bolts of superheated plasma towards its targets. Whether engaged in close-quarters skirmishes or delivering accurate shots at a distance, this sidearm epitomizes the Imperium's commitment to arming its forces with cutting-edge technology.\n\nWith each discharge, the distinct hum of ionized energy accompanies the expulsion of lethal plasma, a testament to the Ryza Plasma Pistol's capability to turn the tide of battle. In the hands of the Astra Militarum's disciplined soldiers, this sidearm stands as a symbol of the Imperium's dedication to providing its warriors with the means to vanquish heresy and alien threats in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Weapons/AM_PlasmaPistol</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.935</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.99</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.77</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.682</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bullet_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>4</warmupTime>
                                <range>22</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>7</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <forcedMissRadius>1.9</forcedMissRadius>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>HP_AM_Plasma_Gun_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                                <targetParams>
                                    <canTargetLocations>true</canTargetLocations>
                                </targetParams>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>5.559</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>6.612</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Mars Inferno pistol</label>
                        <description>Within the sprawling expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 cosmos, the Astra Militarum Mars Inferno Pistol emerges as an epitome of controlled devastation, a sidearm of choice for the disciplined forces of the Imperium. Forged with precision and purpose, this weapon boasts a matte-black ceramite alloy exterior, showcasing its unwavering resilience in the relentless theatre of war.\n\nFunctioning as a potent close-quarters firearm, the Mars Inferno Pistol projects torrents of searing flames towards its targets. Whether in the heat of brutal melee or during precise ranged engagements, this sidearm embodies the Imperium's commitment to equipping its forces with cutting-edge technology for any combat scenario.\n\nWith each discharge, the distinct roar of ignited promethium accompanies the expulsion of deadly flames, a symphony of destruction that signifies the Mars Inferno Pistol's capability to turn the tide of battle. In the hands of the disciplined soldiers of the Astra Militarum, this sidearm stands as a symbol of the Imperium's unwavering dedication to quell heresy and vanquish alien threats in the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.2</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/AM_MeltaPistol</texPath>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>4.2</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.66</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.825</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.99</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.88</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>0.85</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>SpacerGun</li>
                            <li>GW_SM_Ranged</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bullet_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>4</warmupTime>
                                <range>10</range>
                                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>5</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                                <forcedMissRadius>1.0</forcedMissRadius>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>HP_AM_Melta_Gun_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
                                <targetParams>
                                    <canTargetLocations>true</canTargetLocations>
                                </targetParams>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>5.559</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>6.612</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef Abstract="True" ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseHumanMakeableGun" Name="MPBFPM_GW_AM_BolterBase">
                        <graphicData>
                            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
                        </graphicData>
                        <tradeTags>
                            <li>GW_AM_SpacerRanged</li>
                        </tradeTags>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_BolterBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_BoltPistol_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Bolt Pistol</label>
                        <description>In the expansive tapestry of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Bolt Pistol, a formidable sidearm, emerges as a symbol of lethal precision and close-quarters firepower within the arsenal of the Space Marines. This compact yet potent weapon is crafted with a matte-black ceramite alloy, ensuring durability amidst the grim and relentless nature of the galactic battlefield.\n\nThe Bolt Pistol operates as a rapid-firing, self-loading, and magazine-fed firearm, unleashing mass-reactive bolts or projectiles with every precise shot. These explosive bolts, possessing destructive potential upon impact, prove effective against a diverse array of adversaries, showcasing the versatility required in the Space Marine's relentless combat engagements.\n\nFunctioning as a hybrid weapon, the Bolt Pistol seamlessly bridges the gap between conventional sidearms and small-scale artillery. Its deadly accuracy, impactful shots, and rapid firing rate make it a fearsome asset, delivering devastating salvos while maintaining precision in the chaos of close to mid-range combat.\n\nWielding the Bolt Pistol, the Space Marines epitomize the unmatched might and cutting-edge technology of the Imperium of Man, showcasing their unwavering resolve in the eternal struggle against the countless threats that plague the war-ravaged galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.1</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/bolt_pistol</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Autopistol</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>2.8</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.715</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.77</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.88</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.825</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.105</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_BoltPistol_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.9</warmupTime>
                                <range>24</range>
                                <burstShotCount>1</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Bolt_Pistol_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>10.791</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>10.791</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_GW_AM_BolterBase" Name="GW_AM_Gun_Bolter_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>persona Locke Bolter</label>
                        <description>In the sprawling tapestry of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Locke Bolter, a distinctive and specialized firearm, emerges as a testament to the precision and adaptability required by the elite forces within the Imperium. This unique bolter, named after its illustrious inventor or revered user, is meticulously crafted with a matte-black ceramite alloy, ensuring resilience in the face of the galaxy's relentless tumult.\n\nOperating as a rapid-firing, self-loading, and magazine-fed weapon, the Locke Bolter unleashes mass-reactive bolts or projectiles with unparalleled precision. These specialized bolts, engineered for optimal performance, carry devastating potential upon impact, proving effective against a broad spectrum of adversaries. The Locke Bolter serves as a pinnacle of versatility, adapting to the demanding needs of the battlefield.\n\nWith its deadly accuracy, impactful shots, and swift firing rate, the Locke Bolter transcends the ordinary, distinguishing itself as a symbol of excellence among the arsenal of the Imperium. Wielded by the most skilled and revered warriors, it stands as a beacon of technological prowess and unwavering dedication in the ceaseless conflict that defines the grim and war-torn galaxy of Warhammer 40,000.\n\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</description>
                        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
                        <graphicData>
                            <drawSize>1.1</drawSize>
                            <texPath>Weapons/Locke_Bolt</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <soundInteract>Interact_Rifle</soundInteract>
                        <weaponClasses>
                            <li>RangedHeavy</li>
                        </weaponClasses>
                        <weaponTags>
                            <li>HPRanged</li>
                            <li>ShortShots</li>
                        </weaponTags>
                        <statBases>
                            <Mass>7</Mass>
                            <AccuracyTouch>0.605</AccuracyTouch>
                            <AccuracyShort>0.748</AccuracyShort>
                            <AccuracyMedium>0.924</AccuracyMedium>
                            <AccuracyLong>0.792</AccuracyLong>
                            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.53</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
                        </statBases>
                        <equippedStatOffsets>
                            <MoveSpeed>-0.10</MoveSpeed>
                        </equippedStatOffsets>
                        <verbs>
                            <li>
                                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                                <defaultProjectile>GW_AM_Bullet_Bolter_Bond</defaultProjectile>
                                <warmupTime>0.9</warmupTime>
                                <range>32</range>
                                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                                <soundCast>GW_AM_Bolt_Pistol_Sound</soundCast>
                                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                                <muzzleFlashScale>9</muzzleFlashScale>
                            </li>
                        </verbs>
                        <tools>
                            <li>
                                <label>grip</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>10.791</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <label>barrel</label>
                                <capacities>
                                    <li>Blunt</li>
                                    <li>Poke</li>
                                </capacities>
                                <power>10.791</power>
                                <cooldownTime>1.7</cooldownTime>
                            </li>
                        </tools>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Autogun bullet</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectile/Bullet_Small</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>19</damageAmountBase>
                            <speed>70</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_Stubround_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Stub round</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectile/Bullet_Small</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>20</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1</stoppingPower>
                            <speed>55</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Shotgun blast</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectile/Bullet_Shotgun</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>30</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>4</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.14</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <speed>55</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_Autopistolgrim_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Autopistol round</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectile/Bullet_Small</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>15</damageAmountBase>
                            <speed>55</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A beam of focused light that burns the target.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>22</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.56</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.5</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_LasboltACC_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A beam of focused light that burns the target.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>19</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.56</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.5</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWELMG_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A beam of focused light that burns the target.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>24</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.56</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.5</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_Hellbolt_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Hellgun Lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A concentrated beam of light that burns the target - and often through them.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>24</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.70</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.8</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolttwo_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Lasbolt charged</label>
                        <description>An heavily charged beam of focused light, emitting more heat usual.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <causefireChance>0.08</causefireChance>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>30</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.76</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.8</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmall_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Pistol lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A reduced beam of focused light.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>17</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.40</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.2</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_LaserBullet" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef" Name="VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmalll_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Pistol lasbolt</label>
                        <description>A reduced beam of focused light.</description>
                        <textures>
                            <li>Projectiles/Las_Bolt</li>
                        </textures>
                        <seam>0</seam>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>18</damageAmountBase>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.40</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.2</stoppingPower>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseBullet" Name="GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bullet_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>plasma pistol shot</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectiles/Plasma_Projectile</texPath>
                            <shaderType>TransparentPostLight</shaderType>
                            <drawSize>1.1</drawSize>
                        </graphicData>
                        <thingClass>Projectile_Explosive</thingClass>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>15</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>2</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.7</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <explosionRadius>1</explosionRadius>
                            <speed>100</speed>
                            <explosionEffect>GW_PlasmaEffecter</explosionEffect>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseBullet" Name="GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bullet_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>inferno pistol shot</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectiles/Melta_Projectile</texPath>
                            <shaderType>TransparentPostLight</shaderType>
                            <drawSize>0.9</drawSize>
                        </graphicData>
                        <thingClass>Projectile_Explosive</thingClass>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>22</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>3</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>1.5</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <speed>80</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseBullet" Name="HP_AM_Bullet_PlasmaShot_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Plasma shot</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectiles/Plasma_Projectile</texPath>
                            <shaderType>TransparentPostLight</shaderType>
                        </graphicData>
                        <thingClass>Projectile_Explosive</thingClass>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>46</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.8</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.5</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <explosionRadius>1.6</explosionRadius>
                            <speed>120</speed>
                            <explosionEffect>GW_PlasmaEffecter</explosionEffect>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_BaseBullet" Name="HP_AM_Bullet_MeltaGun_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>Meltagun shot</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Things/Projectiles/Melta_Projectile</texPath>
                            <shaderType>TransparentPostLight</shaderType>
                        </graphicData>
                        <thingClass>Projectile_Explosive</thingClass>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Burn</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>99</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>3</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>2.5</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <speed>70</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_BoltPistol_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>bolt pistol round</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Projectiles/AM_BoltPistol_Proj</texPath>
                            <drawSize>0.8</drawSize>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>22</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>0.7</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.35</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <speed>50</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                    <ThingDef ParentName="MPBFPM_Bullet" Name="GW_AM_Bullet_Bolter_Bond" Abstract="True">
                        <label>bolter round</label>
                        <graphicData>
                            <texPath>Projectiles/AM_BoltPistol_Proj</texPath>
                        </graphicData>
                        <projectile>
                            <damageDef>Bullet</damageDef>
                            <damageAmountBase>35</damageAmountBase>
                            <stoppingPower>1.2</stoppingPower>
                            <armorPenetrationBase>0.55</armorPenetrationBase>
                            <speed>50</speed>
                        </projectile>
                    </ThingDef>
                </value>
            </Operation>

            <Operation Class="XmlExtensions.OptionalPatch">
                <modId>Daria40K.MightyPersonaBondForgePatch</modId>
                <key>Daria40K_MightyPersonaBondForgePatch_GrimWorld40000HammeroftheImperium</key>
                <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>

                <caseTrue>
                    <Operation Class="XmlExtensions.PatchOperationAdd">
                        <xpath>Defs</xpath>
                        <value>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainsword_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainsword_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainshortsword_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainshortsword_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_TrenchShovel_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_TrenchShovel_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CombatKnife_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CombatKnife_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CatachanFang_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CatachanFang_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Eviscerator_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Eviscerator_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerFist_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerFist_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerMaul_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_PowerMaul_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_Agripinaamkii_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_Agripinaamkii_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_Agripinaamkiitanker_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_Agripinaamkiitanker_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_OrlockAutogun_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_OrlockAutogun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_Zarona_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_Zarona_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_Hiveworldautopistol_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_Hiveworldautopistol_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_Heavystubber_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_Heavystubber_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_MilitarumShotgun_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_MilitarumShotgun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="Gun_MilitarumShotgunSawn_Bond">
                                <defName>Gun_MilitarumShotgunSawn_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Rippergun_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Rippergun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelsanctified_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelsanctified_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefoursanctified_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefoursanctified_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_VossPatternsanctified_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_VossPatternsanctified_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelt_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelt_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Accatranfive_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Accatranfive_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Lucius_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Lucius_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefender_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefender_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefendert_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraeldefendert_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Hellgun_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Hellgun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Locke_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Locke_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Longlas_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Longlas_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_Gun_PlasmaGun_Bond">
                                <defName>HP_AM_Gun_PlasmaGun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_Gun_MeltaGun_Bond">
                                <defName>HP_AM_Gun_MeltaGun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_BoltPistol_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_BoltPistol_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Gun_Bolter_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Bolter_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_AutoGun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_Stubround_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_Stubround_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_Shotgungrim_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_Autopistolgrim_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_Autopistolgrim_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_LasboltACC_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_LasboltACC_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWELMG_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWELMG_Bullet_Lasbolt_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_Hellbolt_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_Hellbolt_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolttwo_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolttwo_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmall_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmall_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmalll_Bond" Class="VanillaWeaponsExpandedLaser.LaserBeamDef">
                                <defName>VWEL_Bullet_Lasboltsmalll_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bullet_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_PlasmaPistol_Bullet_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bullet_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_InfernoPistol_Bullet_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_Bullet_PlasmaShot_Bond">
                                <defName>HP_AM_Bullet_PlasmaShot_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_Bullet_MeltaGun_Bond">
                                <defName>HP_AM_Bullet_MeltaGun_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_BoltPistol_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_BoltPistol_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                            <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_Bullet_Bolter_Bond">
                                <defName>GW_AM_Bullet_Bolter_Bond</defName>
                            </ThingDef>
                        </value>
                    </Operation>
                </caseTrue>
            </Operation>
        </caseTrue>
    </Operation>
</Patch>